All right. You're done. Let's look at the solution. All
right. We'll move to WeatherProvider. We start by creating a
third selection query up at the top of our provider,
much like the second query except that we search for
the exact date. Rather than a greater than or equal
date. We then add a function that uses the weather
contract. Functions to get the date and postal code from
the URI. We use the new query we just wrote.
And the same SQLI query builder we used before, since it only defines the join.
And then we just call this function in the
weather with location and date switch statement in our
query. That's it. Those are all the queries we
plan to use for Sunshine, but we still need to
test. Let's go back to test provider. As you
can see, our test has a very, very good model
already. Let's fix up some of these old tests
and close the weather cursor. Now, we can simply copy
this test over. It turns out that the exact
same data is required for our new URI. All
we have to do is to build weather location
with date, instead of saying weather location with start
date, and we should get the same result. Let's
see if that's really true by running our tests.
[SOUND] And our test passed. So, we've now implemented
all of the queries, but we're not done with our
content provider yet. After all, we're not writing
any data into the database through our content provider